How are the presales
for Silent Death looking?
We need this deal.
We were beginning to worry
we might never see you again.
How were finals?
Okay.
Just okay, huh?
You too.
They're gonna unpack.
Mm-hmm.
Will you be sleeping here also?
He's protecting us.
How's it going
with Alexandra?
They broke up.
Now is your chance.
Someone is waiting
for you.
I'm glad to have you back.
Sorry to have to rush off
for work, but I'll be back in a few days.
It's fine, Dad.
We're used to it.
Have you been fighting
with the neighbors again?
Of course you'd deny it.
Breakfast anyone?
What is it?
A mongoose got into
Ben's enclosure and bit him.
Is he okay?
It will get better
in two or three days.
Oh, ok.
I'll send the mongoose
in for testing.
See what the results say...
You never know.
I'll call Lambert later
and see if he can swing by after work
and clean out the cage.
Bring some antibiotics.
Leave Ben locked up
until then.
I will.
Are you excited
Lucy is home?
She has her friends.
The three of us will have
so much fun when I'm back.
Doing what?
I'll think of something.
Lame.
Boring.
Go.
Stay here.
Everything will be fine.
I love you.
I love you too.
I should never
have left you.
You're here now.